prairieecothrifter.com 2011-12-05

# Privacy | Prairie Eco-Thrifter

At **Prairie[Eco](http://prairieecothrifter.com/2011/02/how-to-become-an-earth-friendly-consumer.html "Eco")-Thrifter,** we know that the privacy of your personal information is very important. Here is some information on what types of personal information we collect when you visit and use www.prairieecothrifter.com and how we safeguard your information: 

We never sell your personal information to third parties. The email address you provide in the comments section will not be displayed publicly. If you choose to [subscribe via email](http://feeds.feedburner.com/PrairieEcothriftercom), you will be sent an email each time a new post is published.  You can unsubscribe at any time by simply clicking on the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email. If you are uncomfortable sharing your email address in order to receive regular post updates, you might want to consider subscribing via [RSS feed](http://feeds.feedburner.com/PrairieEcothriftercom).

#### **Log Files**

As with most other sites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (Internet Protocol) address, your ISP (Internet Service Provider,  _eg_. Rogers Cable or AOL), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site, and which pages you visited here.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information like your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a pop-up once in your visit or the ability to login to features such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on prairieecothrifter.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology like cookies or web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers ( _eg._ Google AdSense) information like your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to get to prairieecothrifter.com, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes ( _eg._ showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited ( _eg._ showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

#### Double Click DART Cookies

We may also use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history ( _eg._ if you have been visiting sites about Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when visiting a site about hockey.). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, like your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social insurance number, bank account numbers, or credit card numbers.

You can opt out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs like Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs like accounts or forums.

Deleting cookies does not mean that you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that permanently disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running cookies, a new cookie will be added.

We will take all reasonable measures to ensure that your privacy is protected. If you have any questions or concerns, please [contact me](http://prairieecothrifter.com/contact-2).
